Theresa Seay papers, Inclusive: 1865-2008, undated, Bulk: 1960-2002
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Research, 1865-2002, undated; 4
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Riebe, Floyd, 1996 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Robinson, Thomas, 1977 January 12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Robinson, Thomas, 1996 May 18 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Russia, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Saslaw, Leonard, 1996 April-May (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Secret Service, 1963 November 27 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Sibert, James, 1977 August 29 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Sibert, James, 1978 October 18 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Sibert, James, 1997 September 11 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Sibert, James W., Deposition, 1997 September 11 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Smith, Vernon, 1996 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Spencer, Saundra, 1996 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Spencer, Saundra Kay, 1997 June 5 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Starling, Isabel, 1996 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Stringer, John, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Stringer, John, 1993 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Stringer, John T., 1996 April-June (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Subpoenas, 1995 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Taylor, Janie, 1995 November 24 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Testimony, 1977 September 16 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Tracheotomy, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Travell, Janet, 1996 April 8 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), VanHoesen, John, 1996 September 26 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Vrtacnik, Ken, 1996 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Young, Robert, 1996 October 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Book Proposal, “Bits and Pieces: A Green Beret on the Periphery of the JFK Assassination,” Lt. Col. Daniel Marvin with Allan R. J. Eaglesham, 1994 October 6 (Box 6, Folder 36A)
  - Book Reviews, Gerald Posner’s “Case Closed: LHO and the Assassination of JFK”, 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 36B)
  - Citizens Commission of Inquiry, 1975 July (Box 6, Folder 36C)
  - Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Clippings, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Clippings, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1984-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dallas Police Department (DPD), 1963 November 22 (Box 7, Folder 9A)
  - General Services Administration Requests, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9B)
  - JFK Assassination Material at the Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9C)
  - JFK Death Certificates, 1963 November 22 (Box 7, Folder 9D)
  - JFK Lancer, “The Assassination Chronicles”, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - JFK Lancer, Autopsy, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - JFK Lancer, Commission Exhibits, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - JFK Lancer, Gerald Ford, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - JFK Lancer, Oswald, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - JFK Lancer, Single Bullet theory, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy “Curse”, 1963-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15A)
  - Master Researcher Directory, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15B)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Ballistics, 1992 March 16 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Collection Register, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Conspiracy, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Correspondence, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Court Case, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Jack Ruby, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Martinez, Escamilia, 1964 July 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Microfiche Card, Autopsy, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Microfiche Cards, JFK Exhibit, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Microfiche Cards, Warren Commission, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Mohrenschildt (Jeanne) Statement, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), New Orleans Public Library, 1963 November-December (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Notes, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Oswald Evidence, 1964-1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Oswald-Ruby Connection, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Policies, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Reproduction Forms, 1991-2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Telegram Reports, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Telephone Records, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Telephone Records, 1964 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - National Archives and Records Administration (NARA), Warren Commission, 1964 June 28 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Navy Report, 1963 September 30 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Abraham Lincoln, 1865 April-July (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Andrew Garfield, 1881 July-September (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Conspiracy Death List, 1993 June (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1933 February (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Gerald Ford, 1975 September (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Harry Truman, 1950 November (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, John F. Kennedy (1 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, John F. Kennedy (2 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, John Wilkes Booth, 1977, 1979, 1990-2008 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Richard Nixon, 1974 February 23 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Robert F. Kennedy, 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Ronald Reagan, 1981 March, April (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, Theodore Roosevelt, 1912 October (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Political Assassinations and Attempts, William McKinley, 1901 September (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Presentation Materials, 2005 November 21 (Box 8, Folder 19A)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1963 December 16 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1963 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Photo Evidence, 1963 November 22 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Medical Evidence, 1963 November 22-23 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 April 30 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 February 24 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 January 21 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 January 22 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 January 27 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 June 23 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 March 24 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 May 19 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1964 September 18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1967 June 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1968 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, 1993 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - President’s Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy (Warren Commission), Executive Session, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Script, “A Crisis for Democracy: Corruption in Government,” Ground Zero Minnesota, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6A)
  - Spencer, Saundra Kay, 1963 May 16 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stringer, John T., 1949, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Autopsy Manual, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Autopsy Photos, 1963 November 22 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Photos, 1963 November 22 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), New Orleans, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Crime Scene, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), FBI-Oswald Affiliation, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Interview, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Specter, Arlan, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Correspondence, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), FBI-Oswald Conspiracy, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Acoustical Study, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Reed Edward, 1978 April 21 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Boyers, Chester, 1978 April 25 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Reibe, Floyd Albert, 1978 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Lincoln, Evelyn, 1978 July 5 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Osborne, David, 1978 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Finck, Pierre, 1978 March 12 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Permissions, 1978 March 13 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Clossan, Elsie B., 1978 May 4 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Reis, Harold, 1978 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Congressional Record-House, 1981 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Congressional Record House, 1992 August 11 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Congressional Record-Senate, 1992 July 27 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Hill, Clinton J., undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - United States House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Humes, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Publications, 1967-2005, undated; 5
  The Publication series contains written material collected and written by Theresa Seay. Includes newsletters.
  - Articles by Seay, Jumbled Jargon, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Articles by Seay, Medical Mutants, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Articles by Seay, Supermarket Savvy, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Articles, General, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Articles, Mensa Bulletin, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Assassination Theories, 1967-1993 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Autopsy, 1980-1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Bullets, 1966-1978 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - CIA, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Cuba, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Dan Rather, 1976-1995 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - False Witness, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - General, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - General, Acoustic Evidence, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - JFK Docudrama, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lee Harvey Oswald, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Let Justice Be Done, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Magazine, Extra!, vol 5, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Magazine, Extra!, vol 6, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Magazine, Extra!, vol 7, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. Paine’s Garage, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters, Assassinations-SIG/ Target: Truth, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters, Back Channels, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters, Coverups!, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Echoes of Conspiracy, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Open Secrets, 1994-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, People and the PURSUIT of Truth, 1976 March-1978 April (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, PROBE, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, The Continuing Inquiry, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, The Fourth Decade, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, The Fourth Decade, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, The Third Decade, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, The Third Decade, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, The Third Decade, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Other Assassinations and Attempts, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Photo Evidence, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Real Answers, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Reports, JFK Assassination, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Reports, Warren Commission, 1975-1977, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Reports, Warren Commission, 1966-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Books, 1965-2002; 6
  The Books series contains publications which Seay made substantial marginalia and includes a copy of her dissertation.
  - Books, Assassination in America by James McKinley, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Books, Bloody Treason by Noel Twyman, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Books, Dark Side of Camelot by Seymour M. Hersh, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Books, Death of a President by William Manchester, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Books, Final Disclosure by David W. Belin, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Books, Final Judgment: The Missing Link in the JFK Assassination Conspiracy by Michael Collins Piper, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Books, Final Report of the Assassination Records Review Board by Assassination Records Review Board, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Books, Innocence of Oswald and the JFK Assassins, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Books, Kennedy Assassination and the American Public by Bradley S. Greenberg and Edwin B. Parker, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Books, Kennedy Assassination Cover-up by Donald Gibson, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Books, November 22, 1963: You Are the Jury by David W. Belin, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Books, Oswald, the CIA and the Warren Commission, the Unanswered Questions: A Study Based on the Newly Released Files via the “JFK Records Act” by Peter Kross, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Books, Real Answers by Gary Cornwell, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Books, Secret Service: The Hidden History of an Enigmatic Agency by Philip H. Melanson with Peter F. Stevens, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Books, Six Seconds in Dallas by Josiah Thompson, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Books, Warren Commission and Beyond by Theresa Margaret Carroll Seay, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Media, 1964-1994, undated; 7
  The Media series contains film, computer disks, and VHS. Plans are to digitize these materials in the future.
  - Media, 8mm Film, JFK Film Reel, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Media, Floppy Disk, Lyndon Baines Johnson Presidential Library recordings and transcripts of Telephone Conversations (1 of 2), 1964 January-August (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Media, Floppy Disk, Lyndon Baines Johnson Presidential Library Recordings and Transcripts of Telephone Conversations (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Media, VHS, 11-12-93 JFK Theresa, 1993 November 12 (Box 18, Folder 5)